♪Mighty winds carry me to the heavens♪
♪On a wild steed,
I sing, smiling at the mortal world♪
♪Then the cold night veils the stars♪
♪I fall to the depths, yet walk alone♪
♪I brave countless snowy peaks♪
♪Your lingering warmth still fills
my palm♪
♪Though frost and snow may bar my way♪
♪The light in my eyes will never fade♪
♪With a sword that cleaves the clouds♪
♪With a heart as firm as stone♪
♪Through all I've endured,
I have no regrets♪
♪I'm still the boy I once was♪
=Sword God=
=Episode 5=
It's a high-grade Dao Bone,
and he just crushed it!
He could've given it to me!
That's not all.
He even embarrassed
the Holy Maiden in public.
He completely ignored her advances.
He... he must've lost his mind.
(Classic Zhao Feiyang.)
(What a thick skull!)
That fool actually turned her down.
Interesting.
Zhao Feiyang,
you've got some nerve!
How dare you do something like this?
Do you know how precious
a high-grade Dao Bone is?
You just destroyed it?
Didn't you hear her?
It was mine to begin with.
I'll do whatever I want with it.
You...
(Heavenly Sword Sect)
Zhao Feiyang,
what's with that attitude?
How do you expect me to act?
Be grateful or flatter you?
Do you really intend
to be this heartless?
Do you really think
I'm that desperate for you?
Then tell me,
Chen Qiushui.
Who do you think you are?
Is the Holy Maiden in tears?
Qiushui,
do you want me
to kill him for you?
That brat
is completely heartless!
He deserves to die.
No need.
But...
I know he hates me.
Zhao Feiyang,
one day,
you'll see that I meant well.
Thank you for granting me
the divine-grade Dao Bone.
From this day forth,
I stand with the Heavenly Sword Sect
through life and death!
Holy Maiden,
you're too kind.
By the way,
would you be willing
to be a guest elder of our sect?
An invitation from you
would be an honor.
I accept.
(What a performance, Chen Qiushui!)
(You had a hand
in what happened to Bai.)
(Once I recover,)
(you'll be the first to answer for it!)
Brat,
you'd better not leave
the Heavenly Sword Sect.
Otherwise,
you're dead!
Sect Master,
he's as stubborn as a mule
and twice as unpleasant!
Exactly, Sect Master.
Someone who can't cultivate
with his meridians shattered
is nothing
but a waste of our resources here.
Just now,
he even humiliated the Holy Maiden
in public
and now the Holy Son holds
a grudge against him.
Isn't he putting our sect
in a difficult position?
Sect Master,
I suggest we expel him from the sect!
Same here. Expel him.
Expel him!
We can't do this!
What do you mean?
Senior Brother Zhao was once
our sect's chief disciple.
He did so much for the sect,
making it one of the three great sects
in the Southern Domain
of Shenwu Continent.
Now that he's down,
we're just going to cast him aside?
Isn't that going too far?
That was then.
This is now.
It's true he did a lot for the sect.
But now he's offended too many people.
The sect has supported him
for three years.
We've already done more than enough.
There's no need to continue.
Yes.
According to the sect rules,
if an outer disciple
or servant disciple
fails to become a warrior
within three years,
they will be expelled from the sect.
The three years are up.
It's only reasonable to make him leave.
But...
Zhao Feiyang,
do you have anything to say?
Leave at once!
Who says I'm not a warrior?
Who says I can't cultivate?
What do you mean?
Everyone knows what happened to you.
No Dao Bone, shattered meridians.
How could you possibly cultivate?
How could you become a warrior?
Open your eyes and see for yourself.
♪Through the endless night,
I won't give in♪
♪Boots worn through,
blood stains the mountains♪
(Body Tempering Realm, Stage 1)
♪A legend in the making♪
♪My blood runs hot♪
♪I never lose a fight♪
♪I rise against the odds♪
That's...
That's spiritual energy!
How...
How is this possible?
It really is spiritual energy.
He has a Dao Bone now.
He can cultivate again.
How is this possible?
Oh my!
Well...
He really does have a Dao Bone.
(Body Tempering Realm, Stage 1)
But why can't we tell its grade?
It must be an unranked Dao Bone
he got by sheer luck.
That's why we can't tell its grade.
Stage 1 of the Body Tempering Realm.
His cultivation is very low,
but he has indeed become a warrior.
He can cultivate again.
Sect Master, this is good news.
Indeed, it is good news.
After all, he was once
our chief disciple.
Sect Master,
do you really wish to keep him?
He may be able to cultivate now,
but what he has
is only an unranked Dao Bone.
And he's already past
his prime cultivation age.
His prospects are bleak.
What good will it do to keep him?
But rules cannot be bent.
Zhao Feiyang has become a warrior.
Hasn't he?
Yes.
In that case,
he doesn't have to leave.
Zhao Feiyang.
Sect Master.
Congratulations on your breakthrough
and return to cultivation!
You've contributed greatly to the sect,
but that's all in the past now.
The sect can't keep supporting you
unconditionally.
You have to rise on your own.
Tomorrow is the trial
for outer disciples.
If you pass the trial,
you will be a formal disciple again
and receive the same cultivation
resources as other formal disciples.
Thank you, Sect Master.
Dismissed.
Zhao Feiyang.
This is an Essence Nurturing Pill
I refined myself.
It contains at least
a hundred units of spiritual energy.
If you can cultivate again,
this will be useful to you.
Why him?
Elder Murong is treating him
way too well.
Exactly.
What makes him so special?
(I don't like owing anyone a favor.)
(But refusing in public)
(would embarrass Elder Murong.)
Thank you, Elder Murong.
(Once I become a formal disciple,)
(I can enter the Alchemy Hall)
(and repair all my meridians.)
(My return to my former peak
will be within reach.)
Congrats, Senior Brother Zhao!
You get to stay after all.
Thank you
for speaking up for me.
You used to look out for me.
It was only right
that I spoke up for you.
The disciple trial is tomorrow.
You've been here for three years, right?
Yes.
I...
Looks like I may have to leave.
(Inside this sect,)
(few people would stand up for me.)
(If she goes,)
(I'd be losing)
(one of the only friends I have.)
Senior Brother Zhao,
what are you doing?
This Essence Nurturing Pill
may help you.
There's still some time
before tomorrow's trial.
Absorb and refine it now.
Becoming a warrior should be easy.
But it's a gift from Elder Murong.
It's so precious.
How could I take it?
I can't.
Just take it.
No one's ever treated me this well.
Senior Brother Zhao,
how can I ever repay you?
We're fellow disciples.
Don't be so formal.
Senior Brother Zhao,
actually...
there's something I want to tell you.
Go ahead.
Actually,
I...
I like you.
I've liked you ever since
I first came here three years ago.
I just never had the courage to say it.
But today,
I've decided to tell you
since
you gave me something so precious.
Doesn't that
also mean...
that you have feelings for me?
(Such an innocent girl.)
(I have too much on my shoulders,)
(or else I might not turn her down.)
Cuihua,
I only care about you
as a fellow disciple.
If we mixed other feelings into it,
it'd get complicated.
Besides,
revenge is all I care about now.
I've got no room for anything else.
So let's talk about it later.
I have something to do.
I'll be going.
Zhao Feiyang!
Is it because I'm ugly?
Or because I'm a nobody?
You can just say so.
Don't make up strange excuses
to spare my feelings.
That's not it.
It's not?
How is it not?
You even turned down
the Holy Maiden of Tianxuan Kingdom
in public,
let alone a nobody like me.
That's not true at all.
You've got it wrong, Cuihua.
Take it back.
I don't need your pity!
Cuihua,
you're mistaken.
I don't look down on you at all.
Also,
I've already given it to you.
I won't take it back.
Zhao Feiyang,
I'll impress you!
(Honglian Sword Immortal,
Sword Immortal Island)
(Penglai Sword Immortal,
(Canglan Sword Immortal,
Sword Immortal Island)
(The Three Sword Immortals!)
♪I once stood on high,
drawing spiritual energy into my blade♪
♪I laughed, pointing at the stars,
young and fearless♪
♪Then came my fall,
with frost and snow on my shoulders♪
♪My Dao foundation was damaged,
yet my Dao heart never wavered♪
♪I crossed countless peaks
to find my answer again♪
♪Through endless trials,
my Nascent Soul came♪
♪Heaven and earth my furnace,
I rose from the flame♪
♪No sword in hand,
yet numberless blades obey♪
♪I seek the Dao beyond the clouds♪
♪Unafraid of countless trials♪
♪With this flesh and soul♪
♪I shall forge a new age♪
♪Let thunder and fire crown me♪
♪Let wind and clouds heed me♪
♪At cultivation's peak♪
♪My first resolve remains unchanged♪
♪The sun and moon turn♪
♪I hear the Great Dao ring♪
♪I am the undying flame♪
♪Looking back when dust settles♪
♪At last I see, immortality♪
♪Lives in your smiles.♪